ariess.net 2015-10-17

# ariess@net - A Simple Web-based Learning, Privacy Policy

In a common situation and condition, ariess@net will never practice to disclose personal information to third parties. We may share personal information in two instances. Firstly, we may share personal information with our service providers in order to maintain, enhance, or add to the functionality of the ariess@net web service. Secondly, we may share personal information with third parties such as the government or other entities when required to by law or as required by court order. ariess@net respects the privacy and rights of its visitors. No effort is made to identify individuals without their rights, permissions, and knowledge. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

We have heavy commitment to your privacy and security as why we launch this website. We despise spam, adware, and other malicious scripts that can harm our visitors. We believe people who send spam and those kinds of harmful things should spend time in prison for wasting the world\'s time depends on the rules enforce in all countries respectively. Maintaining the privacy, security, and integrity of your account is very crucial and of paramount importance to us.

### Information Use

We collect information from you when you access on our site. When accessing our site or joining our forum, you may appropriately be asked to enter your private identity. However, you may visit our site anonymously. Therefore, any information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 1. to personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs); 2. to improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you).

### Information Disclosure

We will strictly not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personal information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. 

### Term of Use

Please also visit our Terms of Use section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use and the services of our website at Term of Use. By accessing and using our site, we think that you have understood and considered things regarding to our Privacy Policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our statements in our Privacy Policy, we will definitely inform those changes through this page immediately.
